WJZ-TV Collection R0129.WJZ R0129.WJZ
Stage
- Evening Magazine, 1977-1991; EVMAG; 8 Reels 2 inch videotape: Quad; 4,676 Cassettes
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-03-1978-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-019-011 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 11)
    - Orioles, Summer to Cook, Clean, And Babysit, 1978-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-019-011-01 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 11, Segment 2)
    - Tennis Warm Ups, 1978-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-019-011-03 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 11, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-05-1978-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-019-012 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-05; WJZ-EVMAG-019-013 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 13)
    - Michener's Chesapeake Pt., 1978-07-05; WJZ-EVMAG-019-013-01 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-019-014 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 14)
    - Jaws 2:Susan Ford's Review, 1978-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-019-014-01 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 14, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-06-30-1978-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-019-015 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 15)
    - Buffalo; Geo; Dentist; Re-run, 1978-06-30; WJZ-EVMAG-019-015-01 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 15, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-07; WJZ-EVMAG-019-016 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 16)
    - Baltimore Skateboard Daredevils, 1978-07-07; WJZ-EVMAG-019-016-01 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 16, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-07-1978-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-020-001 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-020-002 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 2)
    - Around The World In 1,095 Days, 1978-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-020-002-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-11-1978-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-020-003 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-11; WJZ-EVMAG-020-004 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 4)
    - Search For Real Mother, 1978-07-11; WJZ-EVMAG-020-004-01 (Mixed materials 19, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-020-005 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 5)
    - Michener's Chesapeake Pt, 1978-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-020-005-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-13; WJZ-EVMAG-020-006 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 6)
    - Mandel's One Year Later, 1978-07-13; WJZ-EVMAG-020-006-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-13-1978-07-14; WJZ-EVMAG-020-007 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-14; WJZ-EVMAG-020-008 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 8)
    - Mammoth Tractor Pull, 1978-07-14; WJZ-ECMAG-020-008-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-17; WJZ-EVMAG-020-009 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 9)
    - Crew Of The Pride, 1978-07-17; WJZ-EVMG-020-009-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-18; WJZ-EVMAG-020-010 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 10)
    - Pose For Playboy For $25,000, 1978-07-18; WJZ-EVMAG-020-010-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 10, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-18-1978-07-24; WJZ-EVMAG-020-011 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 11)
    - Car Stereo Accessories, 1978-07-18; WJZ-EVMAG-020-011-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 11, Segment 1)
    - Andy Gibb + Rettys, 1978-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-020-011-02 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 11, Segment 2)
    - Car Security, 1978-07-24; WJZ-EVMAG-020-011-03 (Mixed materials 20, Segment 11, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-20-1978-07-28; WJZ-EVMAG-020-012 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 12)
    - Blueberry Dessert, Improve Backhand, Sun Burn Remedies, Skydiving, 1978-07-20; WJZ-EVMAG-020-012-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 12, Segment 1)
    - Radishes, 1978-07-21; WJZ-EVMAG-020-012-02 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 12, Segment 2)
    - Marinates, Cauliflower, Improve Forehand, Healthy Tan, Motorcycle, 1978-07-28; WJZ-EVMAG-020-012-03 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 12, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-020-013 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 13)
    - Michener's Hidden Chesapeake, 1978-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-020-013-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-20; WJZ-EVMAG-020-014 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 14)
    - How Short People Live, 1978-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-020-014-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 14, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-21; WJZ-EVMAG-020-015 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 15)
    - Fastest Chicken Puckers', 1978-07-21; WJZ-EVMAG-020-015-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 15, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-24; WJZ-EVMAG-020-016 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 16)
    - Millionaire Works Night Shift, 1978-07-24; WJZ-EVMAG-020-016-01 (Mixed materials 20, Tape 16, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-25; WJZ-EVMAG-021-001 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 1)
    - Linnea In Tattoo Parlor?, 1978-07-25; WJZ- EVMAG-021-001-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-14-1978-08-28; WJZ-EVMAG-022-001 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-15-1978-08-18; WJZ-EVMAG-022-002 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 2)
    - Killing Off Weeds For Fall Lawn, Poem Museum, Car Club, 1978-08-15; WJZ-EVMAG-022-002-01 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 2, Segment 1)
    - Cold Meat Salad, Sugar, 1978-08-18; WJZ-EVMAG-022-002-02 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 2, Segment 2)
    - Guacamole Dip, Colts Vs. Redskins, Effect of Cigarettes, 1978-08-17; WJZ-EVMAG-022-002-03 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 2, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-16; WJZ-EVMAG-022-003 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 3)
    - Earth Is Moving, 1978-08-16; WJZ-EVMAG-022-003-01 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-16-1978-08-17; WJZ-EVMAG-022-004 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-17; WJZ-EVMAG-022-005 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 5)
    - London Fog In Baltimore, 1978-08-17; WJZ-EVMAG-022-005-01 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-18-1978-08-21; WJZ-EVMAG-022-006 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-21; WJZ-EVMAG-022-007 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 7)
    - Hot Metal In Bethlehem, 1978-08-21; WJZ-EVMAG-022-007-01 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-21-1978-08-24; WJZ-EVMAG-022-008 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 8)
    - Caring For Tape Septum, Loose Weight In Calves, Skateboards In Glen Bernie, 1978-08-21; WJZ-EVMAG-022-008-01 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 8, Segment 1)
    - Discount Tennis Equipment, 1978-08-22; WJZ-EVMAG-022-008-02 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 8, Segment 2)
    - Carrot Salad, X-rays Can Be Dangerous, Microwave Ovens + cooking Classes, 1978-08-24; WJZ-EVMAG-022-008-03 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 8, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-22-1978-08-23; WJZ-EVMAG-022-009 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-23; WJZ-EVMAG-022-010 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 10)
    - Multi-Million $ Masterpiece, 1978-08-23; WJZ-EVMAG-022-010-01 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 10, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-24-1978-08-25; WJZ-EVMAG-022-011 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-28-1978-08-30; WJZ-EVMAG-022-012 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-28; WJZ-EVMAG-022-013 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 13)
    - Make Movies Happen, 1978-08-28; WJZ-EVMAG-022-013-01 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-25-1978-09-07; WJZ-EVMAG-022-014 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-022-015 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 15)
    - Build Old Ships, 1979-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-022-015-01 (Mixed materials 22, Tape 15, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-06-27-1978-06-30; WJZ-EVMAG-023-001 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 1)
    - Stop Fungus, Physical Fitness Tests, Dress Shop, 1978-06-27; WJZ-EVMAG-023-001-01 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 1, Segment 1)
    - G.D. Graffiti, Loud Noises, 1978-06-29; WJZ-EVMAG-023-001-02 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 1, Segment 2)
    - Celery, Farrell's, Water, 1978-06-30; WJZ-EVMAG-023-001-03 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 1, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-07-1978-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-023-002 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 2)
    - Rice Salad, Speedy Rubber Stamp Co., 1978-07-07; WJZ-EVMAG-023-002-01 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 2, Segment 1)
    - Vacationing Steve Plonts, Skateboarding, Improve Tennis game, 1978-07-11; WJZ-EVMAG-023-002-02 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 2, Segment 2)
    - Dunhill's, Sore Muscles, BOB "Steak + Eggs", 1978-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-023-002-03 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 2, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-15-1978-09-18; WJZ-EVMAG-024-001 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-18; WJZ-EVMAG-024-002 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 2)
    - Bert Jones, 1978-09-18; WJZ-EVMAG-024-002-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-19; WJZ-EVMAG-024-003 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 3)
    - Live In Teepee, 1978-09-19; WJZ-EVMAG-024-003-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-20-1978-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-024-004 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 4)
    - Exercise Pets, 1978-09-20; WJZ-EVMAG-024-004-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 4, Segment 1)
    - Thigh Exercises, 1978-09-21; WJZ-EVMAG-024-004-02 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 4, Segment 2)
    - Salad with Bacon, 1978-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-024-004-03 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 4, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-21-1978-09-22; WJZ-EVMAG-024-005 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-22; WJZ-EVMAG-024-006 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 6)
    - National Champion Majorettes, 1978-09-22; WJZ-EVMAG-024-006-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-024-007 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 7)
    - Women Tracking Rugby, 1978-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-024-007-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-26; WJZ-EVMAG-024-008 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 8)
    - Teenage Mother 15, 1978-09-26; WJZ-EVMAG-024-008-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-27-1978-09-28; WJZ-EVMAG-024-009 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-28-1978-10-02; WJZ-EVMAG-024-010 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 10)
    - Pesto Sauce, Commodores This Weekend, 1978-09-28; WJZ-EVMAG-024-010-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 10, Segment 1)
    - Corn Fritters, Dandruff, 1978-09-29; WJZ-EVMAG-024-010-02 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 10, Segment 2)
    - Pinballs; Bowling, 1978-10-02; WJZ-EVMAG-024-010-03 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 10, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-29; WJZ-EVMAG-024-011 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 11)
    - Goodyear Blimp, 1978-09-29; WJZ-EVMAG-024-011-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 11, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-02; WJZ-EVMAG-024-012 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 12)
    - Baltimore Cross The Atlantic, 1978-10-02; WJZ-EVMAG-024-012-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 12, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-03; WJZ-EVMAG-024-013 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 13)
    - Miss Black America, 1978-10-03; WJZ-EVMAG-024-013-01 (Mixed materials 24, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-04; WJZ-EVMAG-025-001 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 1)
    - Judy Garlands Other Daughter, 1978-10-04; WJZ-EVMAG-025-001-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-05; WJZ-EVMAG-025-002 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 2)
    - Rode Bike Around World, 1978-10-05; WJZ-EVMAG-025-002-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-06-1978-10-10; WJZ-EVMAG-025-003 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-05-1978-10-06; WJZ-EVMAG-025-004 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-06; WJZ-EVMAG-025-005 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 5)
    - Emergency, 1978-10-06; WJZ-EVMAG-025-005-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-09; WJZ-EVMAG-025-006 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 6)
    - Women On Dragstrip, 1978-10-09; WJZ-EVMAG-025-006-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-09-1978-10-10; WJZ-EVMAG-025-007 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-10; WJZ-EVMAG-025-008 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 8)
    - Party In Hot Tub, 1978-10-10; WJZ-EVMAG-025-008-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-11; WJZ-EVMAG-025-009 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 9)
    - 1 Mile Down In Coal Mine, 1978-10-11; WJZ-EVMAG-025-009-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-11-1978-10-12; WJZ-EVMAG-025-010 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-12; WJZ-EVMAG-025-011 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 11)
    - Games Singles Play, 1978-10-12; WJZ-EVMAG-025-011-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 11, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-13; WJZ-EVMAG-025-012 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 12)
    - Unusual Race For Chesapeake, 1978-10-13; WJZ-EVMAG-025-012-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 12, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-16; WJZ-EVMAG-025-013 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 13)
    - Richard Dreyfuss, 1978-10-16; WJZ-EVMAG-025-013-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-16-1978-10-18; WJZ-EVMAG-025-014 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-16-1978-10-17; WJZ-EVMAG-025-015 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-17; WJZ-EVMAG-025-016 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 16)
    - McDonalds Hamburger School, 1978-10-17; WJZ-EVMAG-025-016-01 (Mixed materials 25, Tape 16, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-18; WJZ-EVMAG-026-001 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 1)
    - National Lampoon, 1978-10-18; WJZ-EVMAG-026-001-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-18-1978-10-19; WJZ-EVMAG-026-002 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-19; WJZ-EVMAG-026-003 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 3)
    - Skylab, 1978-10-19; WJZ-EVMAG-026-003-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-026-004 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 4)
    - Elvis Girlfriend, 1978-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-026-004-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-026-005 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 5)
    - Hall & Oats, 1978-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-026-005-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-24-1978-10-25; WJZ-EVMAG-026-006 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-25; WJZ-EVMAG-026-007 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 7)
    - At Home In Alabama (Original Chewed), 1978-10-25; WJZ-EVMAG-026-007-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-25; WJZ-EVMAG-026-008 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 8)
    - At Home In Alabama, 1978-10-25; WJZ-EVMAG-026-008-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-26; WJZ-EVMAG-026-009 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 9)
    - Snake Venom Factory, 1978-10-26; WJZ-EVMAG-026-009-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-26-1978-10-27; WJZ-EVMAG-026-010 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-30; WJZ-EVMAG-026-011 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 11)
    - Linnea/Grand Ole Opry, 1978-10-30; WJZ-EVMAG-026-011-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 11, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-30-1978-10-31; WJZ-EVMAG-026-012 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-31; WJZ-EVMAG-026-013 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 13)
    - Opry With Minnie Pearl, 1978-10-31; WJZ-EVMAG-026-013-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-10-31-1978-11-01; WJZ-EVMAG-026-014 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-01-1978-11-02; WJZ-EVMAG-026-015 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-01; WJZ-EVMAG-026-016 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 16)
    - Diana Nyad'd 76 Hr. Swim, 1978-11-01; WJZ-EVMAG-026-016-01 (Mixed materials 26, Tape 16, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-02; WJZ-EVMAG-027-001 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 1)
    - Bed Of Nails, 1978-11-02; WJZ-EVMAG-027-001-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-03; WJZ-EVMAG-027-002 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 2)
    - Women Who Box, 1978-11-03; WJZ-EVMAG-027-002-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-03-1978-11-06; WJZ-EVMAG-027-003 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-06; WJZ-EVMAG-027-004 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 4)
    - Rohrer Quintuplets At 4, 1978-11-06; WJZ-EVMAG-027-004-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-07-1978-11-08; WJZ-EVMAG-027-005 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-08; WJZ-EVMAG-027-006 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 6)
    - Hee-Hay, 1978-11-08; WJZ-EVMAG-027-006-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-09; WJZ-EVMAG-027-007 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 7)
    - Smallest Trains, 1978-11-09; WJZ-EVMAG-026-007-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-09-1978-11-10; WJZ-EVMAG-027-008 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-10; WJZ-EVMAG-027-009 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 9)
    - Q.E. II, 1978-11-10; WJZ-EVMAG-027-009-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-13; WJZ-EVMAG-027-010 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 10)
    - Biggest Truck Stop, 1978-11-13; WJZ-EVMAG-027-010-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 10, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-14; WJZ-EVMAG-027-011 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 11)
    - Elvis Hometown, 1978-11-14; WJZ-EVMAG-027-011-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 11, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-15-1978-11-16; WJZ-EVMAG-027-012 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-16; WJZ-EVMAG-027-013 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 13)
    - Kenny Rogers, 1978-11-16; WJZ-EVMAG-027-013-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-17; WJZ-EVMAG-027-014 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 14)
    - Ugly Lovable Dogs, 1978-11-17; WJZ-EVMAG-027-014-01 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 14, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-17-1978-11-20; WJZ-EVMAG-027-015 (Mixed materials 27, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-15; WJZ-EVMAG-028-001 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 1)
    - Won 1 Million Dollars, 1978-11-15; WJZ-EVMAG-028-001-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-20; WJZ-EVMAG-028-002 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 2)
    - We Blow Up Buildings, 1978-11-20; WJZ-EVMAG-028-002-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-21; WJZ-EVMAG-028-003 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 3)
    - Power Volleyball, 1978-11-21; WJZ-EVMAG-028-003-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-21-1978-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-028-004 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-028-005 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 5)
    - I Escaped From A Turkish Prison, 1978-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-028-005-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-23; WJZ-EVMAG-028-006 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 6)
    - Maternity Ward/Wild Animals, 1978-11-23; WJZ-EVMAG-028-006-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-23-1978-11-24; WJZ-EVMAG-028-007 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-24; WJZ-EVMAG-028-008 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 8)
    - Square Dancing Fever, 1978-11-24; WJZ-EVMAG-028-008-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-28; WJZ-EVMAG-028-009 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 9)
    - Junk Yard, 1978-11-28; WJZ-EVMAG-028-009-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-11-30; WJZ-EVMAG-028-010 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 10)
    - The Day I Got Out Of Jail, 1978-11-30; WJZ-EVMAg-028-010-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 10, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-01-1978-12-04; WJZ-EVMAG-028-011 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-04; WJZ-EVMAG-028-012 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 12)
    - Shuffle Bowl, 1978-12-04; WJZ-EVMAG-028-012-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 12, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-05-1978-12-06; WJZ-EVMAG-028-013 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-11; WJZ-EVMAG-028-014 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 14)
    - America's Mightiest Tank, 1978-12-11; WJZ-EVMAG-028-014-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 14, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-11-1978-12-12; WJZ-EVMAG-028-015 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-13; WJZ-EVMAG-028-016 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 16)
    - Hee Haw Honey, 1978-12-13; WJZ-EVMAG-028-016-01 (Mixed materials 28, Tape 16, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-13-1978-12-14; WJZ-EVMAG-029-001 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-15; WJZ-EVMAG-029-002 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 2)
    - Toys Rich Kids Buy, 1978-12-15; WJZ-EVMAG-029-002-01 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-19; WJZ-EVMAG-029-003 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 3)
    - Make Magic On TV, 1978-12-19; WJZ-EVMAG-029-003-01 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-19-1978-12-20; WJZ-EVMAG-029-004 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-20; WJZ-EVMAG-029-005 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 5)
    - Nitecaps, 1978-12-20; WJZ-EVMAG-029-005-01 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-22; WJZ-EVMAG-029-006 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 6)
    - Most Cheerful Sound I Washington, 1978-12-22; WJZ-EVMAG-029-006-01 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-21-1978-12-22; WJZ-EVMAG-029-007 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 7)
    - Christmas Show, 1978-12-22; WJZ-EVMAG-029-007-01 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-26-1978-12-27; WJZ-EVMAG-029-008 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-28-1978-12-29; WJZ-EVMAG-029-010 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-12-29; WJZ-EVMAG-029-011 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 11)
    - We Control The Big Trains, 1978-12-29; WJZ-EVMAG-029-011-01 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 11, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-01; WJZ-EVMAG-029-012 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 12)
    - Circus Showgirl, 1979-01-01; WJZ-EVMAG-029-012-01 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 12, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-01-1979-01-02; WJZ-EVMAG-029-013 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-02; WJZ-EVMAG-029-014 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 14)
    - Work On Baltimore Bridge, 1979-01-02; WJZ-EVMAG-029-014-01 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 14, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-03-1979-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-029-015 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-029-016 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 16)
    - Diamond King, 1979-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-029-016-01 (Mixed materials 29, Tape 16, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-05; WJZ-EVMAG-030-001 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 1)
    - Baltimore Duckpin Champ, 1979-01-05; WJZ-EVMAG-030-001-01 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-05-1979-01-08; WJZ-EVMAG-030-002 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-08; WJZ-EVMAG-030-003 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 3)
    - Embassy Party For Superman, 1979-01-08; WJZ-EVMAG-030-003-01 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-09-1979-01-10; WJZ-EVMAG-030-004 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-09; WJZ-EVMAG-030-005 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 5)
    - Jim McKay, 1979-01-09; WJZ-EVMAG-030-005-01 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-10; WJZ-EVMAG-030-006 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 6)
    - Battled The Atlantic, 1979-01-10; WJZ-EVMAG-030-006-01 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-11; WJZ-EVMAG-030-007 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 7)
    - Neil Diamond, 1979-01-11; WJZ-EVMAG-030-007-01 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-11-1979-01-12; WJZ-EVMAG-030-008 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-12; WJZ-EVMAG-030-009 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 9)
    - Live With Lions, 1979-01-12; WJZ-EVMAG-030-009-01 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-01-15; WJZ-EVMAG-030-010 (Mixed materials 30, Tape 10)